const questionSetOne = [
  {
    question: "1. The International Literacy Day is observed on \nA. Sep 8\nB. Nov 28\nC. May 2\nD. Sep 2\n",
    ans: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "2. The language of Lakshadweep. a Union Territory of India, is \nA. Tamil\nB. Hindi\nC. Malayalam\nD. Telegu\n",
    ans: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "3. In which group of places the Kumbha Mela is held every twelve years? \nA. Ujjain. Purl; Prayag. Haridwar\nB. Prayag. Haridwar, Ujjain,. Nasik\nC. Rameshwaram. Purl, Badrinath. Dwarika\nD. Chittakoot, Ujjain, Prayag,'Haridwar\n",
    ans: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "4. Bahubali festival is related to\nA. Islam\nB. Hinduism\nC. Buddhism\D. Jainism",
    ans: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "5. Which day is observed as the World Standards Day?\nA. June 26\nB. Oct 14\nC. Nov 15\nD. Dec 2",
    ans: "b"
  }

]
const questionSetTwo = [
  {
    question: "6. Which of the following was the theme of the World Red Cross and Red Crescent Day?\nA. 'Dignity for all - focus on women'\nB. Dignity for all - focus on Children'\nC. Focus on health for all\nD. Nourishment for all-focus on children",
    ans: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "7. September 27 is celebrated every year as\nA. Teachers' day\nB. National Integration Day\nC. World Tourism day\nD. International Literacy Day", ans: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "8. Who is the author of 'Manas Ka-Hans' ?\nA. Khushwant Singh\nB.	Prem Chand\nC. Jayashankar Prasad\nD. Amrit Lal Nagar",
    ans: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "9. The death anniversary of which of the following leaders is observed as Martyrs' Day?\nA. Smt. Indira Gandhi\nB. PI. Jawaharlal Nehru\nC. Mahatma Gandhi\nD. Lal Bahadur Shastri", ans: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "10. Who is the author of the epic 'Meghdoot ? \nA. Vishakadatta\nB. Valmiki\nC. Banabhatta\nD. Kalidas",
    ans: "d"
  }


]

module.exports = { questionSetOne, questionSetTwo }